DINH VAN QUY

Medical Representative

Address. 47/2/38 Bui Dinh Tuy St, Binh

Thanh Dist. HCMC

Phone. +84 901 787 497

Email. dinhvanquy148@mail.com



PROFILE

I am a Pharmacist. "The life so short, the craft so long to learn" – Hippocrates.

Enthusiastic, responsible, able to work under high pressure and intensity, adapt quickly with new circumstances.

Effective communication & networking skills specialize in making relationship with people and organizations.

Skillful Event celebrating skills: making ideas, plans and running for team buildings, outdoor games, camping trips.

EDUCATION

2011 - 2016

VO TRUONG TOAN UNIVERSITY OF PHARMACY AND

MEDICINE

Bachelor of Pharmacy (GPA: 7.63)

2008 - 2011

QUOC HOC QUY NHON

High School

EXPERIENCE

2017 - 2018

DKSH VIETNAM – Hospital Key Account Representative

May 2017- June 2018

- Take care of hospitals in charge: Dai Hoc Y Duoc, Hung Vuong, Phap Viet, Tim Tam Duc, Truyen Mau Huyet Hoc.
- Take care of key customers: Chief pharmacist, Finance, Director of Hospital.
- Mastering the process of pharmaceutical and medical devices tender management in hospital.
- Following up to sales process and solving the problems so that can achieve personal target.
- Searching potential customer, consulting customer care and making contract with present customers of the company, coordinating with many principles in bringing the best services for customer.

PROFICIENCY AND SKILLS BRANDING

SELF MANAGEMENT

HOBBIES



Socce



Cooking



Coding, Video Games



Backpacking Tourism